Cherry, is there a better way I should approach this?
Yeah, I think she mainly speaks Cantonese and she always nods or says yes to anybody like nurses or physicians.
But I don't think she wants to be touched today.
I'm so glad I asked.
Would you like to help me wash her arms or would she prefer if I leave the basin here for you too?
Of course I can help with... help her to wash.
Thank you.
Because we are new here, we thought that is a nursing job.
So it's good that I can help her.
I think she'll be more comfortable because I'm closer to her.
Sounds good.
Thank you.
OK, I will let you wash yourself, ok? [Cantonese]
OK.
Thank you.
It’s very cool! [Cantonese]
Would you like to wash your arms, too? [Cantonese]
Ok...